♪ Love you like a brother ♪
♪ Treat you like a friend ♪
♪ Respect you like a lover ♪
♪ Oh-woah, oh-woah, oh-woah ♪
♪ You could bet that ♪
♪ Never gotta sweat that ♪
♪ If you be the cash ♪
♪ I'll be the rubber band ♪
♪ You be the match, I will be a fuse ♪
♪ Boom ♪
♪ Painter, baby, you could be the muse ♪
♪ I'm the reporter ♪
♪ Baby, you could be the news ♪
♪ 'Cause you're the cigarette ♪
♪ And I'm the smoker ♪
♪ We raise the bet ♪
♪ 'Cause you're the joker ♪
♪ Checked off ♪
♪ You are the chalk ♪
♪ And I could be the blackboard ♪
♪ You can be the talk ♪
♪ And I can be the walk ♪
♪ Even when the sky comes falling ♪
♪ Even when the sun don't shine ♪
♪ I got faith in you and I ♪
♪ So put your pretty little hand in mine ♪
♪ Even when we're down to the wire, babe ♪
♪ Even when it's do or die ♪
♪ We can do it, baby, simple and plain ♪
♪ 'Cause this love is a sure thing ♪
♪ You could bet that ♪
♪ Never gotta sweat that ♪
♪ You could be the lover ♪
♪ I'll be the fighter, babe ♪
♪ If I'm the blunt ♪
♪ You could be the lighter, babe ♪
♪ Fire it up ♪
♪ Writer, baby, you could be the quote ♪
♪ If I'm the lyric ♪
♪ Baby, you could be the note ♪
♪ Record that ♪
♪ Saint, I'm a sinner ♪
♪ Prize, I'm a winner and it's you ♪
♪ What did I do to deserve that ♪
♪ Paper, baby, I'll be the pen ♪
♪ Said I am the one ♪
♪ 'Cause you are ten ♪
♪ Real and not pretend ♪
♪ Even when the sky comes falling ♪
♪ Even when the sun don't shine ♪
♪ I got faith in you and I ♪
♪ So put your pretty little hand in mine ♪
♪ Even when we're down to the wire, baby ♪
♪ Even when it's do or die ♪
♪ We can do it, baby, simple and plain ♪
♪ 'Cause this love is a sure thing ♪
♪ Now rock with me, babe ♪
♪ Let me hold you in my arms ♪
♪ Talk with me, babe, yeah ♪
♪ Now rock with me, babe ♪
♪ Let me hold you in my arms ♪
♪ Talk with me, babe ♪
♪ This love, between you and I ♪
♪ As simple as pie, baby ♪
♪ It's such a sure thing ♪
♪ Oh, is it a sure thing ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Even when the sky comes falling ♪
♪ Even when the sun don't shine ♪
♪ I got faith in you and I ♪
♪ So put your pretty little hand in mine ♪
♪ Even when we're down to the wire, babe ♪
♪ Even when it's do or die ♪
♪ We can do it, baby, simple and plain ♪
♪ 'Cause this love is a sure thing ♪
♪ Love you like a brother ♪
♪ Treat you like a friend ♪
♪ Respect you like a lover ♪
♪ Oh-woah, oh-woah, oh-woah ♪